[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：然后我们添加了一个元对象API，让我们可以更好地控制
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Then we added a Meta Object API to give us more control over
对象属性的属性，因此
the attributes of the properties of objects, so
我们可以对发生的事情进行更精细的控制。
we can get much finer control over what's going on.
因此，我们现在有两种类型的属性。
So, we now have two types of properties.
我们有数据属性，这是我们一直拥有的东西，或者只是一些
We have data properties, which are the things we've always had or it's just some
您可以存储在要检索的对象中的数据，并且我们具有访问器属性。
data that you can store in the object to retrieve and we have accessor properties.
我之前给你展示了一个温度对象的例子，在那里我们可以有
I showed you an example earlier with the temperature object where we can have
访问器实际上一直是中的访问器属性
accessors and that's an, actually, have always been accessor properties in
语言，但它们从未接触过你，所以你不能制作它们。
the language, but they were never exposed to you, so you couldn't make them.
所以在DOM中有一些东西像是一个点innerHTML是一个访问器属性，
So there are things in the DOM like a dot innerHTML is an accessor property,
这就是为什么你可以分配一些东西给它，然后发生一些事情。
that's why you can assign something to it and then something happens.
所以有很多人对允许你写东西很感兴趣，
And so there was a lot of interest in allowing you to write stuff,
就像DOM一样糟糕，我们成功了。
which is as crappy as the DOM and we succeeded.
所以废话没有限制，你现在可以写了。
So there's no limit on the crap, you can write now.
所以，我们有物体。
So, we've got objects.
对象由属性组成。
Objects are composed of properties.
每个属性都由属性组成。
Each property is composed of attributes.
每个属性都有四个属性。
Every property has four attributes.
如果您是数据属性，则您的属性是值的、可写的、可枚举的和
If you're a data property, your attributes are value, writable, enumerable and
可配置。
configurable.
如果您是访问者属性，
If you're an accessor property,
您的属性是可枚举的，可配置的，获取和设置的。
your attributes are enumerable, configurable, get and set.
因此，value是属性的实际值。
So, value is the actual value of the property.
Writable是一个布尔值，它确定您是否可以读取或写入它，或者
Writable is a Boolean that determines if you can read it or write it, or
如果你能写的话。
if you can write it.
因此，如果可写为false，则为只读。
So if writeable is false, it's read only.
事实证明，该语言始终具有只读属性，但是
It turns out the language has always had read only properties, but
它从来没有暴露给你。
it was never exposed to you.
所以你不能创造它们，只有语言可以创造它们。
So you couldn't create them, only the language could create them.
所以现在任何人都可以。
So now, anybody can.
可枚举意味着它将出现在一个四个n循环中，或者
Enumerable means it will show up in a four n loop or
将显示在object.keys中。
will show up in object.keys.
如果您关闭它，这意味着它不会显示在枚举中，这
If you turn that off, it means it's not going to show up in enumerations, which
意味着你可以更好地隐藏它，这样它就不会一直被挖掘出来。
means you can hide it a little bit better that it won't get dredged up all the time.
可配置意味着您可以删除它或
Configurable means you can delete it or
如果它是数据属性，则可以将其更改为访问器属性。
you can change it into an accessor property, if it was a data property.
get是一个函数，如果您尝试获取属性并
Get is a function that will be called if you try to get the property and
set是一个函数，如果您尝试设置
set is a function that will be called if you try to set
财产。&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：So
the property. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So
有了这一点，我们就有了两个版本的声明。
having that, we've got two versions of a statement.
第一个语句是您可以在ES3中创建对象文字的方式，并且
The first statement is the way you could create an object literal in ES3 and
第二个在ES5中做了完全相同的事情，您可能是
the second one does exactly the same thing in ES5, and you might be
非常感谢。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：[笑]
thinking thank you very much for that. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [LAUGH]
&GT；&GT；道格拉斯·克罗克福德：那是巨大的。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: That's huge.
所以问题是我们希望能够添加这个功能，但是
So the thing is we wanted to be able to add this functionality, but
我们受到限制，无法添加语法。
we were constrained that we couldn't add syntax.
所以我们想让它成为可能，但我们不能让它变得美好。
So we wanted to make it possible, but we couldn't make it nice.
但至少可能总比不可能好，这就是我们曾经的处境。
But at least possible is better than impossible, which is where we were.
因此，这意味着库现在可以构造对象和
So, this means that a library can now construct objects and
可以控制正在发生的事情。
can have control over what's going on.
因此，对象可以指定它想要继承的对象。
So, an object can designate what it wants to inherit from.
它不需要从对象那里听到原型。
It doesn't have to hear from object.prototype.
它可以从任何东西继承，也可以什么都不继承。
It can inherit from anything or nothing.
以前从来没有这样的选择，现在我们可以这样做
That's never been an option before, now we can do that and
它可以说，这个属性是不可写的。
it can say, this property is not writeable.
它不是可枚举的。
It's not enumerable.
它是不可配置的。
It's not configurable.
所以，我们可以允许你把这些东西锁起来。
So, we can allow you to lock those things down.
一旦你将其中一个设置为假，
And once you set one of those things to false,
它再也不能变回真的了。
it can never be turned back to true again.
所以这给了你一些控制，如果你想锁定你的对象，
So that gives you some control that if you wanna lock your object down,
你现在可以这么做了。
you can now do that.
因此我们添加了一个新方法Object.getProperty，
So we added a new method, Object.getProperty,
这样你就可以利用这些东西了。
which allows you to take advantage of this stuff.
因此，这显示了一个创建附件属性的示例
So, this shows an example of creating an accessory property
而不使用新语法。
without using new syntax.
因此，这与我们之前所做的类似，但是
So this does something similar to what we did before, but
它只使用方法调用和
it's only using method calls and
这个表单的优点是你可以在它周围放一个if，你不会
the advantage of this form is that you can put an if around this and you won't
如果您试图在没有语法错误的浏览器上运行它，则会出现语法错误。
get a syntax error if you're trying to run it on a browser that doesn't have it.
而对于语法形式，您不能在语法错误周围放置if。
Whereas with the syntax form, you can't put an if around a syntax error.
因此，如果您尝试在较旧的浏览器上运行它，
So if you try to run it on an older browser,
它只会失败&GT；&GT；Douglas Crockford：所以
it will simply fail &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So
元对象API包含Object.defined edProperty，
that the Meta Object API contains Object.definedProperty,
我刚给你看过了。
which I just showed you.
Object.DefineProperties，它允许您一次定义其中的几个，并且
Object.defineProperties, which will allow you to define several of these at once and
也是Object.getOwnProperty描述符，它将返回一个对象，
also Object.getOwnProperty descriptor, which will return an object,
它描述属性的属性。
which describes the attributes of a property.
我必须指出，这个制度显然是由委员会设计的。
I should point out that this system was clearly designed by committee.
你有像object.create和这样的东西
You've got things like object.create and
你可以得到像getOwnPropertyDescriptor这样的东西。
you get things like getOwnPropertyDescriptor.
委员会就是这样做的。
Committees do stuff like that.
这些名字是如何起作用的没有一致性。
There's no consistency on how the names work.
我们添加了一些您可能永远不会使用的方法。
We added a couple of methods that you'll probably never get to use.
GetOwnPropertyNames，getPropertyOf。
GetOwnPropertyNames, getPropertyOf.
我们添加了这些
We added these for
安全库的目的是希望在所有其他事情之前运行，并且
the purpose of security libraries that want to run before everything else and
锁定所有Brendan故意未锁定的东西，所以
lockdown everything that Brendan intentionally left unlocked, so
环境现在是安全的，第三方代码可以在您的环境中运行。
that the environment is now safe for third party code to run in your environment.
为了得到所有需要锁定的东西，它需要
And in order to get at everything that needed to be locked down, it needed
专门的访问端口钻进了语言，这样他就可以拿到这些东西了。
special access ports drilled into the language, so he could get at this stuff.
所以，那些图书馆可能会做的就是拿这些。
So, what those libraries are likely to do is take these.
使用它们，然后销毁它们，这样其他人就不能使用它们了。
Use them, then destroy them, so that nobody else can use them.
所以拥有了所有这些东西，
So having all of this stuff,
我们可以做以前做不到的事情。
it becomes possible to do things that we couldn't do before.
例如，这是replace_prototype函数。
For example, this is the replace_prototype function.
它完美地复制了一个物体，
It makes a perfect copy of an object,
除了它现在继承了一个不同的原型。
except that it now inherits from a different prototype.
这是人们多年来一直要求的
That's something that people have been asking for for years and
没有，直到现在没有办法做到这一点。
there is no, until now there was no way to accomplish that.
现在有了。所以函数本身看起来很难看
Now, there is. So the function itself is an ugly looking
函数，但可以将其包装在名称中并
function, but you can wrap that in a name and
现在你可以在你的库中提供它，任何人现在都可以创建一个对象
now you can provide that in your library and anybody can now make an object that's
找到了一个不同的原型。&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：it
got a different prototype. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: It
过去，您可以随时向任何对象添加新属性
used to be the case that you could add a new property to any object at any time
只需给它赋值，现在就可以关闭它了。
simply by assigning to it and you can now turn that off.
如果调用Object.proventExtensions并向其传递一个对象，
If you called Object.preventExtensions and pass it an object,
该对象现在将拒绝接受新属性。
that object will now refuse to accept new properties.
如果您尝试给它一个新的属性，它将抛出一个异常，而不是
If you attempt to give it a new property, it will throw an exception instead and
我们可以走得更远。
we can go even further than that.
我们可以冻结物体。
We can freeze the object.
冻结可防止扩展，并使每个属性都为只读和
Freeze prevents extensions and also makes every property read-only and
不可配置，这意味着它现在是一个不可变的对象，并且
non-configurable, which means it is now an immutable object and
它有一些很好的特性。
that has some nice properties.
这意味着该语言的未来版本可能能够做出一些
It means that future versions of the language may be able to make some
有趣的优化，
interesting optimizations,
因为他们可以假设这个物体不能改变。
because they can make assumptions that this object cannot change.
这意味着我们可以更聪明地为该对象生成代码。
That means we can be smarter in the way we generate code for that object.
这也意味着我们可以把冻结的物体交给第三方
It also means that we can take a frozen object hand it to a third party and
确信第三方不会腐败或
be confident that the third party cannot corrupt or
篡改物体，这是非常有价值的东西，
tamper with the object and that's an extremely valuable thing,
特别是在我们越来越多的派对上做越来越复杂的事情的时候。
particularly as we're doing more and more complicated stuff with more parties.